Mittenthal, Richard Papers 6407
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Employer Speech: A Life Cycle, 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Past Practice and the Administration of Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 10)
- The Rule of Law in Arbitration, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Credibility: A Will-O'-The-Wisp, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 12)
- The Presidential Address: Joys of Being an Arbitrator, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Making Arbitration Work: Alternatives in Designing the Machinery, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 14)
- The Art of Opinion-Writing, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Absenteeism, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 16)
- A Core Commentary: Conduct of the Hearing, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Arbitral Implications: Hearing the Sounds of Silence, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Whither Arbitration, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 19)
- The Ever-Present Past, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 20)
- The Ever-Present Rule of Arbitral Discretion, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 21)
  Labor Arbitration Under Fire
- Reminiscences: Fireside Chat, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Invited Paper: The Heart of the Matter, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 23)
- A View from the Middle of the Valley, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Help Wanted: The Missing Piece in Significant Contract Interpretation Disputes, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Impact of Decay in Determining Back Pay, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Lawyers and Arbitration, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 27)
- The Pursuit of Excellence, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Does Arbitration Take Away Management's Right to Manage?, Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Arbitration of the Steel Wage Structure, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Arbitration Decisions: Dana Corporation, 1956-1964 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Job Description and Classification Manual, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Steel Processing Flow Charts, Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Commencement Address: Milton Mayer, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 34)
  May 14, 1958.
- Management and labor Appraisals and Criticisms of the Arbitration Process., 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 35)
  Dallas L. Jones and Russell A. Smith
- Arbitrators and Judges: Dispelling the Hays' Haze, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 36)
  Saul Wallen
- How Arbitrators Decide Cases, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 37)
  In Arbitration Quarterly, Summer 1992, reprinted from Arbitration Journal, v.27, 1972.
- Address of Ralph T. Seward to the Meeting of New Members of the National Arbitration Association, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Arbitration Award Writing: Style and Logic, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 39)
  Charlotte Gold
- At-Will Employment and the Handsome American: A Case Study of Law and Social Psychology, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 40)
  Theodore J. St. Antoine
- The Common Law of the Workplace, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 41)
  May 1997 Draft
- Colloquium: External Law and Justice, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 42)
- NAA Fall Education Conference, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 43)
- The Common Law of the Workplace, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 44)
  October 1997 Draft
- Labor and Employment Arbitration: What's Justice Got To Do With It?, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 45)
  Dennis R. Nolan
- NAA Continuing Education Conference, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Colloquium: The Changing Legal Framework For Arbitration: Statutory and Judicial Reform, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 47)
- NAA Fall Education Conference, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Code of Professional Responsibility for Arbitrators of Labor-Management Disputes, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Formal Advisory Opinions and Advisory Opinion Summaries, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Remedies in Arbitration: Old Problems Resolved, Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 51)
  David E. Feller
- Reminiscences, Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 52)
  Harold S. Block
- Writing the Opinion, Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 53)
  Charles N, Rehmus